$(document).ready(function() {
   
    var triviaQuestions = [{
        question: "All Life begins with a single _____________",
        answerList: ["tissue", "cell", "microbe", "organ"],
        answer: 1
    },{
        question: "Skin, ears, and kidneys are examples of _____________",
        answerList: ["cells", "organ systems", "organs", "tissues"],
        answer: 2
    },{
        question: "One important function of bones is to produce  _____________",
        answerList: ["blood cells", "tendons", "cartilage", "ligaments"],
        answer: 0
    },{
        question: "Digestion begins in the   _____________",
        answerList: ["large intestine", "small intestine", "mouth", "stomach"],
        answer: 2
    },{
        question: "The human heart has _____________ chambers (rooms).",
        answerList: ["Five", "Four", "Two", "Three"],
        answer: 1
    },{
        question: "The main organ in the respiratory system is the _____________.",
        answerList: ["Trachea", "Diaphragm", "Lung", "Bronchi"],
        answer: 2
    },{
        question: " The central nervous system includes:",
        answerList: ["Spinal Cord", "Brain & Spinal Cord", "Nerves", "Brain"],
        answer: 1
    },{
        question: "What is the term which describes the joining together of a sperm and an egg?",
        answerList: ["Fertilization", "Ovulation", "Reproduction", "Duplication"],
        answer: 0
    },{
        question: "The primary function of the system is to support and protect the body",
        answerList: ["Digestive", "Muscular", "Skeletal", "Respiratory"],
        answer: 2
    },{
        question: "The primary function of this system is to break down food into usable form and to remove waste products",
        answerList: ["Muscular", "Respiratory","Skeletal", "Digestive"],
        answer: 3
    }]
});